thepapermillstore.com 2017-07-06

# Privacy Policy

##  1\. Introduction 

1.1. Effective Date. The effective date of this Privacy Policy is May 15, 2016. 

1.2. Purpose. The Paper Mill Store, Inc. ("The Paper Mill Store" or " **Company** ") is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of the The Paper Mill Store website, the The Paper Mill Store service, and any software applications made available by The Paper Mill Store, such as any mobile device application The Paper Mill Store makes available (together, the " **Service** "). The Paper Mill Store has published this " **Privacy Policy** " to show its commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of privacy. 

1.3. Scope. This Privacy Policy is only applicable to the Service, and not to any websites or services of third parties (" **Third Party Websites** "), which may have data collection, storage, and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Privacy Policy. For additional information, see Section 11 (Third Party Websites) and Section 4.5 (Third Party Cookies and Advertising). 

1.4. Separate Terms of Use. By using the Service, you represent and warrant that you have also read and understood, and agree to be bound by, both this Privacy Policy and The Paper Mill Store's separate Terms of Use document (the " **Terms of Use** "), which is incorporated by reference and made part of this Privacy Policy. The Terms of Use document is available at http://www.thepapermillstore.com/terms-and-conditions. 

1.5. _** No Permission Without Agreement. By using the Service, you represent and warrant that you have read and understood, and agree to the terms of, this Privacy Policy. If you do not understand or do not agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using or accessing the Service.**_

##  2\. Updates and Changes to Privacy Policy. 

2.1. Each time you access the Service, the then-current version of this Privacy Policy will apply. Each time you use the Service, we recommend that you check the date of this Privacy Policy in Section 1.1 (Effective Date) and review any changes since the last time you used the Service. 

2.2. Although most changes are likely to be minor, The Paper Mill Store reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting a new version on this page. Any such addition, update, or change will be effective immediately on posting. Unless The Paper Mill Store obtains your express consent, any revised Privacy Policy will apply only to information collected after the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy, and not to information collected under any earlier Privacy Policy. 

##  3\. Children's Privacy. 

The Paper Mill Store does not solicit or knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If The Paper Mill Store obtains actual knowledge that it has collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, The Paper Mill Store will immediately delete such information from its database. Because The Paper Mill Store does not collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13, The Paper Mill Store has no such information to use or disclose to third parties. The Paper Mill Store has designed this Privacy Policy to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). 

##  4\. Information Collection Practices. 

4.1. Traffic Data. Like most website and mobile application operators, The Paper Mill Store automatically gathers information that web browsers automatically make available, including: (i) IP addresses; (ii) Internet domain names; (iii) types of devices accessing the Service; and (iv) types of Web browsers accessing the Service (collectively " **Traffic Data** "). Traffic Data is anonymous information that is not meant to personally identify you. 

4.2. Cookie Policy. " **Cookies** " are text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit or certain emails that you open. Cookies store a string of information on a user's computer or mobile device, which the user's web browser provides to the Service automatically each time it interacts with the Service. The purpose of Cookies is to identify the user as a unique user of the Service. The Paper Mill Store uses two types of Cookies: "first-party cookies" and "third-party cookies." 

4.3. First Party Cookies. The Paper Mill Store uses first-party Cookies on the Service, for example the Google Analytics Cookie, for the following purposes: (1) to gather visitor and access information relevant to customizing the Service to your interests; and (2) to store your password so you do not have to re-enter it each time you use the Service. 

4.4. _**If you do not wish to have first-party Cookies placed on your computer or mobile device, you should set your web browser to refuse Cookies before accessing the Service. However, certain features of the Service may not function properly without the aid of Cookies. If you refuse Cookies, you assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality.**_

4.5. Third Party Cookies and Advertising. 

  * 4.5.1. Advertising on Third Party Websites. The Paper Mill Store may advertise on other Third Party Websites to you after you access the Service. We and third-party marketing partners, including without limitation Google, Inc. (" **Google** "), may use first party Cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie), third party Cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie), and web beacons (such as the Facebook conversion tracking pixel, see <https://www.facebook.com/business/a/online-sales/conversion-tracking>), including across multiple devices, to inform, optimize, and serve advertisements to you based on your use of the Service. This practice is commonly known as retargeting or remarketing (see <https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Behavioral_retargeting>).
  * 4.5.2. Google Analytics. 
    * 4.5.2.1. Google Analytics is Google's analytics tool that helps website and app owners to understand how their visitors engage with their properties. It may use a set of cookies to collect information and report website usage statistics without personally identifying individual visitors to Google. The main cookie used by Google Analytics is the "__ga" cookie. The Paper Mill Store uses Google Analytics on the The Paper Mill Store website.
  * 4.5.3. Optimizely. The Paper Mill Store uses Optimizely to test the effects of changes to the Website on users' browsing experiences. Information on what data Optimizely stores about users, how it is collected, and how it is used are available in Optimizely's privacy policy, available at <https://www.optimizely.com/privacy/>.
  * 4.5.4. Data Collection by Third Parties. Any of these third parties may place Cookies on your computer or mobile device, use web beacons (see <https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Web_beacon>), and gather IP addresses and log data to collect traffic and activity data to deliver relevant metrics and content.
  * 4.5.5. Other Analytics and Data Services. Some specific third party data services The Paper Mill Store uses and their privacy policies are: Crazy Egg (<http://www.crazyegg.com/privacy>), Facebook Connect (<https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/>), Algolia (<https://www.algolia.com/policies/privacy>), Zopim (<https://www.zendesk.com/company/privacy/>), Bing (<https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement/default.aspx>), Bronto (<http://bronto.com/terms/privacy-policy>), PowerReviews (<http://www.powerreviews.com/privacy-policy/>), Google+ (<https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/?hl=en>), Twitter (<https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en>), Pinterest (<https://about.pinterest.com/en/privacy-policy>). Because The Paper Mill Store updates the Website from time to time, this may not be an exhaustive list.
  * 4.5.6. Opting Out of Third Party Cookies. 
    * 4.5.6.1. You may customize your Google Cookies preferences or opt out of using Google Cookies on the Google Ads Settings page at <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>.
    * 4.5.6.2. You may learn about Facebook Cookies and how to customize your preferences at <https://www.facebook.com/about/ads>.
    * 4.5.6.3. You may opt out of using other third parties' Cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. You can also learn more about how to delete or control Cookies at <http://www.aboutcookies.org/>.

4.6. Personally Identifiable Information. To use certain features of the Service, you will be asked to provide The Paper Mill Store certain personally identifiable information (" **Personal Information** "). Personal Information includes the following categories, without limitation: (1) " **Contact Data** " (such as your name, phone number, fax number, mailing address and email address); (2) " **Financial Data** " (such as your credit/debit card number and expiration date); (3) " **Demographic Data** " (such as your gender and ZIP code); and (4) "Third Party Social Media Account Data" (such as your account information for third party social media accounts when you access the Service in connection to those accounts). In each case, you will be asked to provide Personal Information; the Service will not gather it secretly. The Paper Mill Store may supplement the Personal Information you provide with additional Personal Information gathered from public sources or from third parties (e.g., consumer reporting agencies) who may lawfully provide that information to The Paper Mill Store. You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information, with the caveat that your refusal to do so may prevent you from using certain features of the Service. 

4.7. Specific Information Collected. The Paper Mill Store collects the following specific items of Personal Information: 

  * 4.7.1. your first and last name
  * 4.7.2. your address
  * 4.7.3. your email address
  * 4.7.4. your telephone number
  * 4.7.5. birth date

4.8. Information You Make Public. The Service may contain features (e.g., instant messages, electronic messaging, etc.) that allow you to upload, post, transmit, display, perform, or distribute content, or other information, including your Personal Information. Any information that you choose to disclose by means of such features becomes public information over which The Paper Mill Store is unable to exercise control. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information by means of such features, and you agree to assume all responsibility for doing so. 

##  5\. Information Use and Disclosure Practices. 

5.1. Traffic Data and Information Gathered Using Cookies. The Paper Mill Store analyzes Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies to help The Paper Mill Store better understand who is using the Service and how they are using it. By identifying patterns and trends in usage, The Paper Mill Store is able to better design the Service to improve your experience, and to serve you more relevant and interesting content. From time to time, The Paper Mill Store may release Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Service. The Paper Mill Store does not attempt to link information gathered using Cookies to Personal Information. 

5.2. Personal Information. 

  * 5.2.1. Generally. The Paper Mill Store uses your Contact Data to send you information about The Paper Mill Store and The Paper Mill Store's products and services, and to contact you when necessary in connection with the Service. The Paper Mill Store uses your Financial Data to verify your qualifications for certain features of the Service and, when necessary, to bill you. The Paper Mill Store uses your Demographic Data to customize and tailor your experience on the Service. The Paper Mill Store uses your Third Party Social Media Account Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy and the privacy policies of third party social media companies, such as Facebook and Twitter. As with Traffic Data and information gathered using Cookies, from time to time The Paper Mill Store may release Demographic Data in the aggregate, such as by publishing a report on trends in the usage of the Service.
  * 5.2.2. Disclosure Practices. Except under the following categories of circumstances, The Paper Mill Store will keep your Personal Information private, and will not share it with third parties. 
    * 5.2.2.1. Disclosure to Marketing Partners. The Paper Mill Store may use any Personal Information to help our clients better understand the demographics of our target audiences, as well as to support our marketing data products and services. We may also provide personally identifiable data to partner firms which may include third party marketing companies, affiliates, advertising agencies, and data aggregation companies. Your Personal Information may be used by these partner firms to provide consumers with information on products and services that may be of interest in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
    * 5.2.2.2. Disclosure in Connection with Service. The Paper Mill Store discloses Personal Information to those who help it provide services, including without limitation those who perform technical, administrative, and data processing tasks such as hosting, billing, fulfillment, data storage, and security.
    * 5.2.2.3. Social Media. At your direction, The Paper Mill Store discloses your information and your use of the Service on social media platforms. The Paper Mill Store sends your information through the APIs of social media platforms you authorize, in compliance with all applicable laws and the applicable platforms' privacy policies in place when your information is sent.
    * 5.2.2.4. User Content. 
      * 5.2.2.4.1. User Content Defined. " **User Content** " is any content, material, or information, not including Personal Information, that you submit, upload, and/or post to, or transmit, display, perform, or distribute by means of, the Service, whether in connection with your use of the Service or otherwise. This includes, without limitation, personal photos and videos.
      * 5.2.2.4.2. License to User Content. As stated in the Terms of Use, by using the Service, you grant The Paper Mill Store, Inc. and its stockholders, officers, directors, employees, agents, affiliates, consultants, representatives, sublicensees, successors, and assigns (collectively, the " **Company Parties** ") the right to publish your name and any username of yours in connection with the Company Parties' exercise of their license in and to your User Content. You further waive any claims arising from the Company Parties' exercise of that right. For additional information, see the section of the Terms of Use titled "User Content".
    * 5.2.2.5. By Law or to Protect Rights. The Paper Mill Store discloses Personal Information when required to do so by law, or in response to a subpoena or court order, or when The Paper Mill Store believes in its sole discretion that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of The Paper Mill Store, third parties, or the public at large.
    * 5.2.2.6. Business Transfers; Bankruptcy. The Paper Mill Store reserves the right to transfer all Personal Information in its possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of The Paper Mill Store's assets. Other than to the extent ordered by a bankruptcy or other court, the use and disclosure of all transferred Personal Information will be subject to this Privacy Policy, or to a new privacy policy if you are given notice of that new privacy policy and an opportunity to affirmatively opt out of it. Personal Information submitted or collected after a transfer, however, may be subject to a new privacy policy adopted by The Paper Mill Store's successor organization.

##  6\. Consent to Receive Electronic Communications From Company. 

Without limitation, by registering for the Service and/or by providing your name, email, postal or residential address, and/or phone number through the Service, you hereby expressly consent to receive electronic and other communications from The Paper Mill Store, over the short term and periodically, including email communications, regarding the Service, new product offers, promotions, and other matters. You may opt out of receiving electronic communications at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each communication. 

##  7\. Consent to Receive Electronic Communications from Partner Marketers. 

Without limitation, by registering for the Service and/or by providing your name, email, postal or residential address, and/or phone number through the Service, you hereby consent to receive, and openly and knowingly solicit, electronic communications, including email communications, from The Paper Mill Store partner firms, which may include third party marketing companies, affiliates, advertising agencies, and data aggregation companies regarding their services, including offers, promotions, and other related matters. You may opt out of receiving electronic communications at any time by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in each communication. 

##  8\. Security of Personal Information. 

The Paper Mill Store takes security seriously. We use commercially reasonable safeguards to protect against the unauthorized access, use, modification, destruction, or disclosure of your Personal Information. However, due to the realities of data security, The Paper Mill Store is unable to guarantee that any information provided to us will not be accessed, hacked, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by unauthorized parties. 

##  9\. Lost or Stolen Information. 

You must promptly notify us if your credit, bank, other financial institution information, username, or password is lost, stolen, or used without permission. In such an event, we will remove that credit card number, bank account information, other financial institution information, username, or password from your account and update our records accordingly. 

##  10\. User Ability to Access, Update, and Correct Personal Information. 

The Paper Mill Store wants your Personal Information to be complete and accurate. As stated in the Terms of Use, by using the Service, you represent and warrant that all information you provide in connection with your use of the Service is current, complete, and accurate, and that you will update that information as needed to maintain its completeness and accuracy. To confirm the completeness and accuracy of, or make changes to, your Personal Information, visit your personal profile. Through your personal profile, you may review and update your Personal Information that we have already collected. 

##  11\. Third Party Websites. 

The Paper Mill Store neither owns nor controls Third Party Websites. Accordingly, Third Party Websites are under no obligation to comply with this Privacy Policy except with respect to Personal Information provided directly to them by The Paper Mill Store. Before visiting or providing Personal Information to Third Party Websites, you should inform yourself of the privacy policies and practices (if any) of those Third Party Websites, and should take those steps necessary to, in your discretion, protect your privacy. 

##  12\. Promotional Activities. 

From time to time, The Paper Mill Store may conduct contests, giveaways, and other promotions (collectively, " **Promotional Activities** "). Any information submitted in connection with Promotional Activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy Policy. From time to time, The Paper Mill Store may also ask you to participate in surveys designed to help The Paper Mill Store improve the Service. Any Personal Information provided to The Paper Mill Store in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey, and will be disclosed to third parties not bound by this Privacy Policy only in aggregated form. 

##  13\. Business Transitions. 

In the event The Paper Mill Store goes through a business transition, including without limitation any merger, acquisition, partnership, business reorganization, debt finance, or sale of company assets, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership (together a " **Business Transition** "), The Paper Mill Store may use information collected in accordance with this Privacy Policy and subject to its restrictions, as part of any such Business Transition. In such instances, your information can be part of the assets transferred. 

##  14\. Do-Not-Track Disclosure. 

The Paper Mill Store does not respond to "Do Not Track" signals sent by browsers.
